export const questions = [
    {date: "December 1, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 1), day: 1, question: "What is 825 divided by 4?", answer: "206r1"},
    {date: "December 2, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 2), day: 2, question: "What is 723 times 6?", answer: 4338},
    {date: "December 3, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 3), day: 3, question: "Where is Esperanza originally from, in “Esperanza Rising”? ", answer: "aquascalientes"},
    {date: "December 4, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 4), day: 4, question: "In “Esperanza Rising”, what sickness does Mama have?", answer: "valley fever"},
    {date: "December 5, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 5), day: 5, question: "If Ms. Draeger has 423 bees and they need to go into 4 hives, how many bees go into each hive?", answer: "105r3"},
    {date: "December 6, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 6), day: 6, question: "Santa Claus brings 4 toys to the Smith household, 3 toys to the Andrew’s household, and 6 toys to the Thomas household. How many toys did he bring all together?", answer: "13 toys"},
    {date: "December 7, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 7), day: 7, question: "What is ½ of 4?", answer: 2},
    {date: "December 8, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 8), day: 8, question: "What is ⅚ + ¾?", answer: "1 7/12"},
    {date: "December 9, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 9), day: 9, question: "What is Ms. Draeger’s classroom theme?", answer: "bees"},
    {date: "December 10, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 10), day: 10, question: "Crouton gets fed an entire pile of food each day. She gets fed ⅘ of her food in the morning, how much does she get fed in the evening?", answer: "1/5"},
    {date: "December 11, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 11), day: 11, question: "In “Esperanza Rising”, a girl keeps talking about striking, who is she?", answer: "marta"},
    {date: "December 12, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 12), day: 12, question: "Frosty the Snowman wants to make sure he won’t melt on vacation, what temperature is the freezing point in Farenheit?", answer: "32 degrees"},
    {date: "December 13, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 13), day: 13, question: "What is 4,231 times 8?", answer: 33848},
    {date: "December 14, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 14), day: 14, question: "What is 975 divided by 5? ", answer: 195},
    {date: "December 15, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 15), day: 15, question: "What does the ‘P’ in PEMDAS stand for (in math terms)?", answer: "parenthesis"},
    {date: "December 16, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 16), day: 16, question: "When multiplying fractions by a whole number, what does the word ‘of’ mean?", answer: "multiply"},
    {date: "December 17, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 17), day: 17, question: "What is Kaiser’s mascot?", answer: "leopard"},
    {date: "December 18, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 18), day: 18, question: "When writing, what does the ‘C’ stand for in RACE?", answer: "cite evidence"},
    {date: "December 19, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 19), day: 19, question: "What are Isabel’s younger siblings names in the book, “Esperanza Rising”?", answer: "pepe and lupe"},
    {date: "December 20, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 20), day: 20, question: "If Emiliano baked a pumpkin pie with 8 slices and Axzhatly ate half of the pie, how many slices did Axzhatly eat?", answer: "4 slices"},
    {date: "December 21, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 21), day: 21, question: "What is the name of Santa’s reindeer with a glowing red nose?", answer: "rudolph"},
    {date: "December 22, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 22), day: 22, question: "According to the movie “Elf”, what are elves' main four food groups?", answer: "candy candy canes candy corns and syrup"},
    {date: "December 23, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 23), day: 23, question: 'Finish the song lyrics: “Jingle bells, Jingle Bells, Jingle ______"', answer: "all the way"},
    {date: "December 24, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 24), day: 24, question: "If Santa ate 4 cookies at every house he visited and he visited 9,423 houses, how many cookies did he eat?", answer: "37692 cookies"},
    {date: "December 25, 2020", dataDate: new Date(2020, 11, 25), day: 25, question: "What day do you come back from winter break on?", answer: "january 5th"},
]